Vonnegut, Bernard; Papers ua902.068
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Manuscripts, 1867-1997; Undated; 7; 8.57 cubic ft.
  - Article: "Comparison between Electrical Processes Occurring Over Land and Over water", 1985-1986 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Article: "A Continuous Recording Condensation Nuclei Meter", 1950 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - Article: "Corona Produced by Splashing of Water drops on a Water Surface in a Strong Electric Field", 1973-1974 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Article: "Counting Sodium-Containing Particles in the Atmosphere by their Spectral Emission in a Hydrogen Flame", 1953 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Article: Crude Altimeter, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Article: "Deductions Concerning Accumulations of Electrified Particles in Thunderclouds Based on Electric Field Changes Associated with Lightning", 1980-1983 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Article: "The Design, Construction, and Use of an Ice Crystal Counter for Ice Crystal Cloud Studies by Aircraft", 1970 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Article: "Desirable Requirement for Scientific Papers Describing Weather Modification Experiments", 1966 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27)
  - Article: "Detachment of Pendant Water Drops by High Voltage Poises", 1975 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 28)
  - Article: "Detection and Measurement of Aerosol Particles", 1952 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Article: "Direct Measurement of Vertical Potential Differences in the Lower Atmosphere", 1958; 1970; 1973 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Article: "Downdrafts in Cumulus Clouds", 1955 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Article: "Early Experiments Seeding Cumulus with AgI", 1970-1972 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Article: "Effects of a Lightning Discharge on an Airplane", 1965-1967 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Article: "Effect of Atmospheric Space Charge on Initial Electrification of Cumulus Clouds", 1963 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Article: "Effect of Halogens on the Production of Condensation Nuclei by a Heated Platinum Wire", 1953 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Article: "Effect of Sunlight on the Action of Silver Iodide Particles as Sublimation Nuclei", 1951 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Article: "The Effect of Temperature on the Strength and Fatigue of Glass Rods", 1946 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 37)
  - Article: "Electric Discharges Inside Tornadoes", 1976-1978; 1980 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 38)
  - Article: "Electric Field Perturbations Caused by Eruptions of Yellowstone Geysers", 1962 (Oversized 4, Folder 13)
  - Article: "Electric Field Perturbations Caused by Eruption of Yellowstone Geysers", 1962-1963 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 39)
  - Article: "Electric Potential Above Ocean Waves", 1973-1974; 1977 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 40)
  - Article: "Electric Potential Gradients Above Thunderstorms", 1966 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 41)
  - Article: "Electric Potential Gradient Measurements Near Icelandic Geyser & Steam Plume From Geothermic Wall", 1964-1965 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 42)
  - Article: "Electrical Activity Associated with the Blackwell-Udall Tornado", 1957 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 43)
  - Article: "Electric Balance in the Lower Atmosphere", 1971-1973; 1977 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 44)
  - Article: "Electrical Breakdown Caused by Dust Motion in Low-Pressure Atmospheres: Considerations for Mars", 1973; 1977 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 45)
  - Article: "Electrical Measurements Over Thunderstorms", 1989 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 46)
  - Article: "Electrical Rainfall Intensity Sensor", 1978 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 47)
  - Article: "Electrical Theory of Tornadoes", 1960 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 48)
  - Article: "Electricity in Volcanic Clouds", 1965 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 49)
  - Article: "Electrostatic Hazards Associated with the Transfer and Storage of Liquid Hydrogen", Undated (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 50)
  - Article: "Electrostatic Technique for Measuring Velocity of Small Projectiles in Transit Through Glass Barrell", 1967; 1971; 1974-1975 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 51)
  - Article: "Enhanced Charge Transfer in Dielectric Fluids Containing Particles", 1967 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 52)
  - Article: "Estimated Possible Effects of AgI Cloud Seeding on Human Health", 1972 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - Article: "Estimates of Raindrop Collection Efficiencies in Electrified Clouds", 1960 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2)
  - Article: "Evaporation of Lava & Its Condensation from the Vapor Phase", 1965-1966 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 3)
  - Article: "An Explanation for Anomalous Lightning from Forest Fire Clouds", 1991-1995 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Article: "An Explanation for Anomalous Lightning from Forest Fire Clouds", 1991-1995 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Article: "Eye Witness Tornado Observations Obtained with Telephone and Tape Recorder", 1969-1973 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Article: "Fair-Weather Atmospheric Electric Potential Gradient and Space Charge Over Central Illinois, Summer 1960", 1962 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - Article: "Formation of Condensation by Airplane Propellers", 1989 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - Article: "Formation of a Vortex by an Elevated Electrical Heat Source", 1970-1971 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Article: "Further Comments on 'Note Potentialities Cumulonimbus Hurricane Seeding Experiments'", 1965 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10)
  - Article: "Further Comments re: Note Potentialities Cumulonimbus and Hurricane Seeding Experiments", 1965 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 11)
  - Article: "Generation of a Vortex by Electrical Heating", 1969 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12)
  - Article: "Giant Electrical Storms", 1959 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 13)
  - Article: "Gushes of Rain and Hail", 1964-1965 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 14)
  - Article: "Gushes of Rain and Hail", 1964 (Oversized 4, Folder 14)
  - Article: "Gushes of Rain and Hail" Diagrams, 1962; Undated (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Article: "Historical Note on the Nucleation of Ice Formation by Silver Iodide", 1946-1947; 1968-1971 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)
  - Article: "How the External Currents Flowing to a Thundercloud Influence its Electrification", 1990 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Article: "Humidity Required for Ice Nucleation from the Vapor onto Silver Iodide and Lead Iodide Aerosols over the Temperature Range -6C to -67C", 1980-1981 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18)
  - Article: "Hydrometer-Type Float Method for Measuring Surface and Interfacial Tensions", 1942 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 19)
  - Article: "Ice Nucleating Capabilities of Silver Iodide and Lead Iodide at Low Temperatures", 1979 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Article: "Ice Nucleation by Precipitated Silver Iodide Silver Bromide", 1971-1972 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - Article: "Ice Nucleation in a Supercooled Cloud by Cul-3 AgI and AgI Aerosols", 1973-1974 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Article: "Ice Nucleation by Miersite", 1973-1974 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Article: "Ice Nucleation by Solid Solutions of Silver Copper Iodide", 1972-1973 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Article: "Importance of Evaporative Cooling in the Formation of Thundercloud Downdrafts", 1994-1996 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Article: "Importance of Including Time in the Specification of the Ice Nucleus Concentrations", 1951; 1975; 1977; 1985-1988 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Article: "Influence of Butyl Alcohol on Shape of Snow Crystals Formed in the Laboratory", 1948 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27)
  - Article: "In Response to Polar Initiative Proposal for further Simple Meteorological Experimentation", 1996 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 28)
  - Article: "Inside the Tornado", 1968; 1972 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Article: "Inside the Tornado", Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 15)
  - Article: "Initiation of Freezing in Supercooled Cloud Droplets by Ionizing Radiation", 1979-1980 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Article: "Instruments for Measuring Meximum Thunderstorm electrified Field Intensity", 1973 (Flat-file 6)
  - Article: "Instrument for Measuring Maximum Thunderstorm Electric Field Intensity", 1974-1975 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Article: "Investigation of the Pseudobinary Solid Solutions of AgI-Cul by means of X-ray Diffraction", 1971-1975 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Article: "Langmuir's Seeding of Hurricanes", 1970 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Article: "Lattice Spacings of Pseudobinary Solid Solutions of Silver Bromide and Silver Iodide", 1971 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Article: "Lightning Induced Brightening in the Airglow Layer", 1992 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Article: "Lightning to the Ionosphere?", 1980-1981 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Article: "Locations of Charged Regions in Thunderclouds Inferred from Electric Field Charges Associated with Lightning", Undated (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 37)
  - Article: "Lowlight Level TV Images of Lightning from Space", 1963; 1984 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 38)
  - Article: "Luminosity Accompanying St. Louis Tornado- February 10, 1959" (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 39)
  - Article: "Luminous Phenomena in Nocturnal Tornadoes", 1966 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 40)
  - Article: "Luminous Phenomena in Nocturnal Tornadoes", 1966 (Oversized 4, Folder 16)
  - Article: "Measurements of the Electrical Conductives of Air Over Hot Water", 1987 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 41)
  - Article: "Measurements of Maximum Electric Field Intensities Over Water During Thunderstorms", 1975-1977 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 42)
  - Article: "Mesoscale Observations of Lightning from Space Shuttle", 1985 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 43)
  - Article: Merit Students Encyclopedia, "Lightning," "Lightning Rod", 1977-1978 (Box 3 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 44)
  - Article: "Meteorological Phenomenon called Crown Flash", 1971 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - Article: "Miniature Vortices Produced by Electrical Corona", 1992 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2)
  - Article: "Miniature Whirlwinds Produced in the Laboratory by High-Voltage Electrical Discharges", 1970 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 3)
  - Article: "Misconceptions about Cloud Seeding with Dry Ice", 1952-1981 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Article: "A Modification of the Telescope and Scale System for Increased Accuracy in the Measurement of Galvanometer Deflections", 1941 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Article: "Modified Cine Sound Camera for Photographing Thunderstorms and Recording Lightning", 1975; 1977-1978 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Article: "Motion-Picture Time-Lapse Photography from High-Altitude Balloons", 1958 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - Article: "New Type of Freezing-Point Apparatus. Freezing Points of Dilute Lanthanum Chloride Solutions", 1960 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - Article: "Nightime Observations of Thunderstorm Electrical Activity from a High-Altitude Airplane", 1984-1985 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Article: "Note on Nuclei for Ice Crystal Formation", 1949 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10)
  - Article: "Nucleation Ice Crystals in Supercooled Clouds Caused by Passage of an Airplane", 1948; 1950; 1983-1986 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 11)
  - Article: "Nucleation of Ice Formation in Supercooled Clouds as a Result of Lightning", 1965 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12)
  - Article: "Noctornul Photographs Taken From a U-2 Airplane Looking Down on Tops of Clouds Illuminated by Lighting", 1975; 1985; 1988-1989 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 13-14)
  - Article: "Observations of Lightning in the Stratosphere", 1995 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Article: "Observations of Optical Lightning emissions from above Thunderstorms Using U-2 Aircraft", 1983 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)
  - Article: "Orientation of Ice Crystals in the Electric Field of a Thunderstorm", 1965 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Article: "Oscillatory Anemometer", 1985-1986 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18)
  - Article: "Oscillatory Vane for Measuring Speed of Gas Flow", 1987-1988 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 19)
  - Article: "Photographs of Lightning from the Space Shuttle", 1982-1983 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Article: "Possible Consequences of Global Dispersion a Krypton 85", 1974-1975 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - Article: "A Possible Effect of Lightning Discharge on Precipitation Formation Process", 1960 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Article: "Precipitable Water", 1961 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Article: "Preliminary Attempts to Influence Convective Electrification in Cumulus Clouds by the Introduction of Space Charge into the Lower Atmosphere", 1959 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Article: "Production of Ice Crystals by the Adiabatic Expansion of Gas", 1948 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Article: "Production of Monodisperse Liquid Particles by Electrical Atomization", 1952-1953 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Article: "Quaint Cumulus Convection Conviction", 1997 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27)
  - Article: "Radar Observations of Rain Gushes Following Overhead Lightning Strokes", 1962 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 28)
  - Article: "Recent Experiments on the Effect of Ultraviolet Light on Silver Iodide Nuclei", 1951 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Article: "Recent Observations of Lightning Discharge from the Top of a Thundercloud into the Clear Air Above", 1989 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Article: "Reduction of Thunderstorm Electric Field Intensity Produced by Corona from a Nearby Object", 1983-1984 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Article: "Relationships Between Thunderstorm and Weather Electricity", 1958 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Article: "Repeated Nucleation of Supercooled Water Sample", 1982-1984 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Article: "Repeated Nucleation of a Supercooled Water Sample that Contains Silver Iodide Particles ", 1982-1984 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Article: "Report of Cloud Physics Committee", 1967 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Article: "Response Characteristics of an Oscillatory Vane for Flow-Speed Measurements", 1986-1988 (Box 4 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Article: "Response to Earle Williams' Letter in Scientific American of July 1989", 1988-1989 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - Article: "Results of an Experiment to Determine Initial Precedence of Organized Electrification and Precipitation in Thunderstorms", Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2)
  - Article: "Ripple at the Edge of a Spreading Monomolecular Film", 1943 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 3)
  - Article: "The Role of the Space Shuttle Videotapes in the Discovery of Sprites, Jets, and Elves", 1998 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Article: "Rotating Bubble Method for the Determination of Surface and Interfacial Tensions", 1942 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Article: "The Science of Rainmaking", 1951 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Article: "Simple Electrometer Employing an Electrified, Nonconducting Fiber", 1957 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - Article: "Simultaneous Observations of Lightning Radiations from Above and Below Clouds", 1979-1980 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - Article: "The Smell of Tornadoes", 1997 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Article: "Solar Sector Weather Relationships", 1974 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10)
  - Article: "Some Observations of Thunderstorms from Above", 1984 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 11)
  - Article: "Some Scientific Objectives of a Satellite-Borne Lightning Mapper", 1983 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12)
  - Article: "Stabilization of a High-Voltage Discharge by a Vortex", 1960 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 13)
  - Article: "The Structure of Crystalline Bromine", 1936 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 14)
  - Article: "Tape Recorder Photocell Instrument for Detecting and Recording Lightning Strokes", 1975 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Article: "Technique for Introduction into Atmosphere of High Concentrations of Electrically Charged Aerosol Particles", 1966-1967; 1971 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)
  - Article: "Technique for the Introduction into the Atmosphere of High Concentrations of Electrically Charged Aerosol Particles", Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 17)
  - Article: "Technique for Introducing Low-Density Space Charge into the Atmosphere", 1961 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Article: "Technique for Producing Uniform Small Droplets by Capillary Waves Excited in a Small Meniscus", 1981-1981 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18)
  - Article: "Tests to Determine in the Conductivity of Air is Increased by Humidification", 1982; 1987 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 19)
  - Article: "Thin Films of Supersaturated Solutions for Detecting, Counting, and Identifying Very Small Crystalline Particles", 1952 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Article: "Thundercloud Electricity", 1964-1965 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - Article: "Thunderstorm Electrification", 1966 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Article: "Time-Lapse Photography of Clouds from High Altitude Balloons", 1969-1970 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Article: "Time-Lapse Photography of Clouds from High Altitude Balloons", 1970 (Oversized 4, Folder 18)
  - Article: "Top Weather Event of 1981-Flight of the Space Shuttle", 1982 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Article: "Tornado", 1969 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Article: "Tornadoes in Labor", 1972 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Article: "Unusual Electrical Discharges Associated with Whirlwinds from Volcano Clouds", 1966 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27)
  - Article: "Validity of C.T.R Wilsons Hypothesis Concerning the Global Atmospheric Electrical Circuit", 1981-1985 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 28)
  - Article: "Variation with Temperature of the Nucleation Rate of Supercooled Liquid Tin and Water Drops", 1948 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Article: "A Very Brief Introduction to Meterology for those to whom the Field is new", 1996-1967 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Article: "Visual Analogue of Radar Bright Band Phenomenon", 1960 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Article: "Visual Confirmation of the Junction Process in Lightning Discharges", 1960 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Article: "Vortex Thermometer for Measuring True Air Temperatures and True Air Speeds in Flight", 1950 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Article: "A Vortex Whistle", 1953 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Article: "What Happens to the Electric Charge Being Carried to Upper Surface of a Thundercloud by the C.T.R Wilson Current?", 1984 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Article: "When will We Change the Weather", 1967 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Article: "Whirlwinds Produced by Eruption of Surtsey Volcano", 1964; Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 37)
  - Article: "Whirlwinds Produced by the Eruption of Surtsey Volcano", Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 19)
  - Article: "Wilson Cloud Chamber Effect Under Natural Conditions", 1962 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 38)
  - Article: "Wind Speed Estimation Based on the Penetration of Straws and Splinters into Wood", 1976 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 39)
  - Article: "Wind Speeds Required to Drive Straws and Splinters into Wood", 1975-1976 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 40)
  - Article: "Wind Speeds Required to drive Straws and Splinters into Wood", 1976 (Oversized 4, Folder 20)
  - Article: "World Around Us - Inside the Tornado", 1971-1972 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 41)
  - Article about Science Article on Toledo, Tornado, 1966 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 42)
  - Atmospheric Electrification, 1948; 1955-1956; 1958 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 43)
  - Atmospheric Electricity, 1967; 1970; 1978; 1990-1991 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 44)
  - Balloon Borne Equipment Suspension & Isolation, 1962 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 45)
  - Book: Electrified Particles in the Lower Atmosphere (Unpublished), 1966; 1968 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 46)
  - Book Review: "Atmospheric Electrodynamics", 1985 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 47)
  - Book Review: "The Earth's Electrical Environment", 1987 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 48)
  - Book Review: "Lightning", 1969 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 49)
  - Book Review: "Understanding Lightning", 1971 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 50)
  - Book Review: "Weather Modification by Cloud Seeding", 1982 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 51)
  - Campaign to Improve Quality of Time Life Books, 1965-1971 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 52)
  - Chapter: Atmosphere Electrostatics" Book Chapter, 1971; 1973-1974 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 53)
  - Chapter: "The Physics of Thunderclouds", Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 54)
  - Chapter: "The Thundercloud", 1974-1977; 1979 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 55)
  - Chapter: "Thunderstorm Theory", 1965 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 56)
  - Charge Release, 1956; 1962 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 57)
  - Charts, 1959; Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 58)
  - Chinese Articles with Mr. Huang, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 59)
  - Comments from Ross Gunn on Montreaux Paper, 1963 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 60)
  - Comments on Readers Digest, Passage on Lightning, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 61)
  - "Condensation of Water Vapor to Form Cloud & Fog Droplets", Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 62)
  - Contributions to Technical Papers, 1965 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 63)
  - Corona Current Detector, 1961 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 64)
  - Correspondence Regarding Technology Review Article, 1966-1967 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 65)
  - Cumulus Studies, Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 66)
  - Data, Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 67)
  - Data, Notes, 1898; 1954; 1959; Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 68)
  - Data: "Spray Nozzle Type Silver-Iodide Smoke Generator for Airplane Use", Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 20)
  - Draft: "Spray Nozzle Type Silver-Iodide Smoke Generator for Airplane Use", 1951 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 69)
  - Drafts of Papers on Thunderstorm Electrification, 1981; 1985 (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 70)
  - Dr. Wiederhorn's Bibliography, Undated (Box 5 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 71)
  - Early Papers Submitted to Scientific Journals, 1961-1962 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - Electrical Theory of Tornadoes, 1956-1960; 1974 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2-3)
  - Electrical Theory of Tornadoes Drawings, 1953; 1955; 1957 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Electrometer Readings, Undated (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Encyclopedia Americana: Cloud Seeding, 1967 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Encyclopedia Americana: Lightning, 1971 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - Encyclopedia Americana: Rain, 1971-1972; 1979 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - Encyclopedia Americana: Tornadoes, 1970 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1966-1970 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10-11)
  - Exchange with Keith & Saunders on "Light Emission from Colliding Ice Particles", 1988-1989 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12)
  - Extracts from Hearings on Weather Legislation, 1951 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 13)
  - Fiber Electrometer Drawings, Undated (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 14)
  - Filter Illustrations, 1958 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Funk and Wagnalls Encyclopedia Entry on Lightning, 1975 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)